Mss.B.St65p
American Philosophical Society
Joseph Stokes, Jr. Papers
1920-1972
Mss.B.St65p
American Philosophical Society
147.0 Linear feet Ca. 140,000 items, 147 linear feet
Ca. 140,000 items, 147 linear feet.
This large collection primarily centers on Stokes' administration and research at the Children's Hospital of Philadelphia. A Philadelphia pediatrician, Stokes had many interests in the areas of infectious diseases, public health and environmental control, and all are reflected in this collection. There is a long series covering his work at the Children's Hospital, including individual correspondence from many staff members.
Stokes, Joseph, 1896-1972
Box 1-294
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Presented by Frances Stokes and accessioned, 09/26/1972 (1973 259ms); additional papers presented by Frances Stokes and accessioned, 05/08/1974 (1974 667ms).
Biographical/Historical note
Joseph Stokes, Jr. graduated from the University of Pennsylvania School of Medicine in 1920. Four years later he became an instructor of pediatrics at the Medical School. In 1939, he was named William Bennett Professor and chairman of the Department of Pediatrics, and physician-in-chief of the Children's Hospital of Philadelphia. He is credited with transforming Children's Hospital into a world center of pediatric teaching and research. His scientific efforts include the study and control of infectious diseases, especially the development of passive protection against epidemic hepatitis and poliomyelitis, as well as active immunization of epidemic influenza. For his work on the control of infectious hepatitis among World War II serviceman, Dr. Stokes was awarded the Medal of Freedom. He retired from Children's Hospital of Philadelphia and the University of Pennsylvania Medical School in 1963.
Physiology, Biochemistry, and Biophysics Note
Students of physiology, biochemistry, or biophysics may be interested in the following materials:
Cohn, Edwin J. (Edwin Joseph), 1892-1953 ( Includes minutes of formed elements meeting.) Correspondence (5 folders) 1945-1953 English
Cohn, Edwin J. (Edwin Joseph), 1892-1953. Gamma globulins. ( Contains material on Cohn's wartime, blood-fractionation project. Includes correspondence with Charles A. Janeway and Elizabeth Pennock Maris.) Correspondence (3 folders) 1943-1945 English
Committee on Blood and Blood Derivatives ( Contains material on Cohn's wartime, blood-fractionation project.) Records (39 folders) 1949-1951 English
Additional Biographical Notes:
Edwin Joseph Cohn established his research program in protein chemistry in 1920 at the department of physical chemistry of Harvard Medical School. Integrating the intellectual approaches of his mentors -- Lawrence J. Henderson, Frank R. Lillie, Thomas B. Osborne, and S. P. L. Sorensen -- and adapting his combined program to the concerns of a medical institution, Cohn addressed a variety of physiological problems of clinical relevance. However, fundamental investigations of the physical chemistry of proteins and amino acids remained a major focus throughout his tenure at Harvard. These studies (in collaboration with John T. Edsall, John Kirkwood, J. L. Oncley, and Jeffries Wyman) led to the discovery of important correlations between the structures of proteins and their physical properties, such as solubilities, ionization, and spectra.
One of Cohn's most important accomplishments, and a major contribution to biomedical knowledge of the Committee on Medical Research, was his blood-fractionation project. An enormous enterprise involving biochemists, physiologists, clinicians, and other life scientists, the project yielded purified serum albumin for treatment of shock, gamma globulins for immunization, and numerous other protein fractions of blood plasma. Cohn's procedures were scaled up for industrial distribution for military and civilian uses. This project also yielded new information about blood chemistry and physiology. The Stokes Papers contain a great deal of material on Cohn's war project. Some of this material may be found in the files dealing with research on gamma globulins, and in the files on the Committee for Blood Fractionation.
American Academy of Pediatrics.; American Friends Service Committee.; American Medical Association.; American Pediatric Society.; American Philosophical Society.; Association of American Physicians.; Barbero, Giulio John, 1923-; Bayne-Jones, Stanhope, 1888-1970; Benison, Saul; Bernstein, Yale B.; Bongiovanni, Alfred M., 1921-; Chapple, Charles C., 1903-; Child Guidance Clinic (Philadelphia, Pa.).; Children's Hospital of Philadelphia; College of Physicians of Philadelphia; Committee of Physicians for the Improvement of Medical Care.; Communicable Disease Center (U.S.); Gittings, J. Claxton, (John Claxton), 1874-1950; Gregg, Alan, 1890-1957; György, Paul, b. 1893; Harris, Susanna, 1919-; Harris, Tzvee N., 1912-; Haverford College.; International Congress of Pediatrics.; National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis.; Paul, John Robertson, 1917-; Philadelphia Pediatric Society.; Playtex Park Research Institute.; Rhoads, Jonathan Evans, 1907-2002; Rose, John A.; Salk, Jonas, 1914-1995; Shope, Richard E., (Richard Edwin), 1901-; Society of American Bacteriologists.; Somers, Anne Ramsay; UNICEF.; United States. -- Army Epidemiological Board.; University College of the West Indies (Mona, Jamaica); University of Pennsylvania.; Wolman, Irving Jacob, 1905-1978; Woods Schools.; Arthritis.; Cerebral palsy.; Cystic fibrosis.; Epidemiology.; Family Planning.; Gamma globulins; Hepatitis.; Influenza.; Japan; Measles.; Medicine.; Metabolic disorders in children.; Mumps; Pediatrics.; Poliomyelitis; Public health.; Quakers -- Pennsylvania -- Philadelphia.; Travel -- Russia
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Aaron, Harold, 1967
  - Abadie, Jules, 1944
  - Abelson, Neva, 1954-1955
  - Abelson, Philip H., 1955
  - Abrahamov, Abraham, 1971
  - Abt, Isaac Arthur, 1952
  - Aceto, Thomas, Jr., 1955
  - Ackerly, S. Spafford, 1959
  - Ackoff, Russell L., 1971-1972
  - Acosta, Melinda, 1962
  - Adam, Doris Jean D., 1955, 1960
  - Adams, Forrest H., 1964
  - Adams, Arlin M., 1967
  - Adams, Raymond D., 1961
  - Adams, William Curtis, 1962
  - Adamson, William C., 1955, 1959-1960
  - Addison, John, 1963
  - Adler, Marty, 1966
  - Adler, Stuart W., 1954
  - Advances in Pediatrics, 1946, 1964
  - Agerty, Horst A., 1951-1959
  - Aiken, Robert B., 1971
  - Air-Shields, Incorporated, 1954-1955
  - Albrecht, Robert M., 1954
  - Album, Fredlyn, 1971
  - Album, Manuel, 1964
  - Alderfer, Harold H., 1954-1955
  - Alderman, Donald B., 1957
  - Aldrich, Robert A., 1955-1963
  - Aldridge, Fred C., 1958
  - Alexander, Benjamin, 1969
  - Alexander, J. Deaver, 1955-1956
  - Alexandrov, Igor, 1959-1960
  - Allam, Mark W., 1969
  - Allcock, Jennifer A., 1967
  - Allen, Fred H., 1956
  - Allen, Fred M.B., 1955-1956, 1962
  - Allen, J. Garrott, 1954, 1962
  - Allen, James H., 1971
  - Allen, Richard, 1954-1955, 1958
  - Allen, Rose, 1955
  - Allen, Wilmar M., 1950, 1955-1956
  - Allmond, Bayard W., 1960
  - Almanac, 1971
    Scope and Contents note
    Gaines, Karen C.
  - Almy, William E., 1949-1967
  - Alpern, Anne X., Undated
  - Alpha Mu Pi Omega, 1951-1954
  - Alpha Omega Alpha, 1950-1951, 1968
  - Alther-Diener, Huldi, 1951-1957
  - Altman, Ronald, 1961-1962
  - Alvarado, Jorge, 1961
  - Alvarez, Walter C., 1960
  - Alway, Robert H., 1956-1957
  - Amberson Associates, 1955-1956
    Amberson, Roseanne
  - Amend, Edie, 1967
  - Amenta, William and William Hough, 1964
  - American Journal of Epidemiology, 1965
  - American Sterilizer Company, 1954
  - Ames, Mary Daniel, 1948-1966
  - Amira, Mrs. Charles, 1962
  - Anbari, Rachad, 1960-1961
  - Anchor Serum Company, 1959
  - Andereck, Janet M., 1965, 1967
  - Anderson, Arnold S., 1967
  - Anderson, Arthur Forrest, 1950, 1955
  - Anderson, Carl M., 1969
    Merck Company Foundation.
  - Anderson, H.B., 1941
  - Anderson, H.D., 1964
  - Anderson, John A., 1956
  - Anderson, John M., 1946
  - Anderson, John R., 1956
  - Anderson, Norman G., 1964
  - Anderson, Odin W., 1962
  - Anderson, Paul S., Jr., 1968
  - Anderson, S. Gray, 1947-1950, 1959
  - Anderson, Thomas F., 1962
  - Anderson, William B., 1954-1955
  - Anderson, William S., 1965-1970
  - Andrews, Christopher H., 1944-1945, 1950-1956
  - Andrews, D.A., 1970-1971
  - Andrews, Justin M., 1953, 1957
  - Andux, Albert, 1960
  - Andzaparidze, O.G., 1969
  - Angell, Donald, 1964
  - Annals of Internal Medicine, 1970
  - Annandale Farms, 1952, 1955
  - Annenberg, Walter, 1959
  - Anson, Mrs. William R., Jr., 1965
  - Anthony, Sister Rose, M.S.B.T., 1961
  - Appel, Kenneth E., 1952, 1961-1965
  - Appleton-Century-Crofts, Inc., 1953-1955
  - Apt, Leonard, 1961
  - Arcasoy, Mufit, 1959, 1962
  - Archetti, Italo, 1959
  - Architect, 1950-1964; 3.0 folders
  - Arcia, J.R., 1955
  - Arey, James B., 1970
  - Aring, Charles D., 1949
  - Armour Pharmaceutical Company, 1968-1969
  - Arnett, John H., 1960
  - Arniel, Gavin C., 1956
  - Aronberg, Elaine, 1969
  - Aronson, Jason, 1960
  - Arthur D. Little Company, 1957
  - Asay, Lyal D., 1960-1961
  - Asbell, Milton B., 1959
  - Ascoli, Marion R., 1954
  - Ash, Rachel, 1950-1959, 1969, undated
  - Ashby, Dwight R., 1963
  - Ashmead, Duff, 1971
  - Ashton, William, 1967
  - Ashwell, Gilbert, 1960
  - Ashworth, Salli, 1963
  - Association Press, 1964
  - Atchley, Dana W., 1963
  - Atchlie, Kathleen, 1961
  - Athenaeum of Philadelphia, 1972
  - Athreya, Balu H., 1958-1970
  - Aub, Joseph C., 1951, 1961-1971
  - Audio Digest, 1961-1963
  - Audiophone Company, 1964
  - Auer, Edward T., 1963
  - Auerbach, Robert, 1963
  - Austin, J. Harold, 1941
  - Australia, 1953-1955
  - Austrian, Robert, 1964-1967
  - Avery, Gordon B., 1958
  - Avicolla, Elizabeth, 1967
  - Awards, 1937-1950
  - Ayusawa, Iwao, 1966-1969
  - Ayusawa, Jun, 1972
  - Babbitt, James A., 1941
  - Babbott, Frank L., 1958-1960
  - Babcock, Barbara, 1967
  - Baby talk, 1950, 1958
  - Bach, Frederick C., 1949
  - Bachman, Carl, 1947-1948, 1961
  - Bachman, Leonard, 1959-1967
  - Bachrach, William H., 1955
  - Backstrand, Jerald, 1946
  - Backus, Philip S., 1957
  - Bacon, Edmund N., 1966-1967
  - Bacon, Emily P., 1952-1953, 1966
  - Bacon, Francis R., 1951
  - Bacon, J.E., 1952
  - Bacon Memorial Library, 1957
  - Bacon, S. Allen, 1969
  - Baehr, George, 1950
  - Baer, Mrs. Gordon R., 1956-1957
  - Bar, Hans, 1953-1954
  - Bailey, Charles P., 1949-1959
  - Bailey, Wilbur, 1962
  - Baily, Kamilla, 1965
  - Bain, Katherine, 1946-1967
  - Baird, William J., 1942
  - Baker, Arthur G., 1968
  - Baker, David, 1961
  - Baker Laboratories, Inc., 1957
  - Baker, Mrs. P.J., 1941
  - Baker, Richard F., 1945
  - Bakwin, Harry, 1947-1964
  - Ball, Eric G., 1946
  - Ballanco, Suzanne K., 1966-1967
  - Balls, Kent F., 1959
  - Balsam, Alan, 1953-1954, 1960
  - Banana Flakes, 1942, 1945
  - Banatvala, J.E., 1963
  - Bancroft, Jean M., 1960
  - Bancroft School, 1958
  - Bandeira, Jorge de Sousa, 1954, 1956
  - Bang, Frederik B., 1950-1967
  - Baratucci, Mary E., 1967-1970
  - Baratz, J. Joseph, 1951
  - Barba, Philip S., 1941-1945, 1965
  - Barba, William P., 1947, 1952-1963
  - Barber, G. Winston, 1949
  - Barbero, Giulio, 1947-1966; 2.0 folders
  - Barden, Robert P., 1942
  - Baren, Martin, 1959-1961
  - Barker, Clyde F., 1968-1969
  - Barker, M. Herbert, 1945-1947
  - Barnard, Chester I., 1952
  - Barnell, J.D., 1962
  - Barnes, Alta, 1943
  - Barnes, Don J., 1945
  - Barnes, Mrs. George W., Jr., 1947
  - Barnes, J. Hampton, 1966, 1968
  - Barnes, Lewis A., 1959-1966
  - Barness, Lewis N., 1949-1951
  - Barnett, Henry L., 1956-1957
  - Barnett, Russell J., 1947
  - Barnwell, John B., 1959
  - Barol, Daniel H., 1949-1962, undated
  - Barol, Samuel, 1953
  - Barondess, Jeremiah A., 1951-1956
  - Barr, Arthur N., 1941
  - Barr, Richard G., 1956-1957
  - Barrows, Mr. and Mrs. Dan, 1969
  - Barrows, Donald B., 1951
  - Barsky, Joseph M., Jr., 1952
  - Barsky, Paul, 1965
  - Bartels, Donita J., 1960
  - Barth, Eivind, 1961
  - Bartholomew, Henry H., 1948
  - Bartram, John B., 1965-1968
  - Basecka, Maria, 1969
  - Bashe, Winslow J., Jr., 1951-1963
  - Basman, Jack, 1953
  - Bass, Murray H., 1950
  - Bassett, David R., 1962-1969
  - Bassett, Miyoko, 1959-1968
  - Bates, Sanford, 1945
  - Bates, William, 1942, 1958
  - Batson, Blair E., 1955-1956
  - Batson, Randolph, 1962
  - Battaglia, Joseph, 1957
  - Battles, Winthrop H., 1967
  - Baty, James Marvin, 1942
  - Bauer, Frank L., 1962-1963
  - Bauer, Johannes H., 1941
  - Bauer, Walter, 1961
  - Baughman, J.L., 1949
  - Baum, Carl, 1964
  - Baumann, Arnold W., 1949
  - Baumgartner, Leona, 1948, 1954, 1969
  - Bauza, Carlos, 1949-1962
  - Baxter, A. Laurence, 1943
  - Baxter, Paul, 1950-1954
  - Bayer, Joseph F., 1959
  - Bayley, John, 1961
  - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope, 1944-1970
  - Bazley, Percival, 1961
  - Beacon Press, 1968
  - Beadle, Walter J., 1953, 1957, 1970
  - Beale, A.J., 1959
  - Bean, William B., 1968
  - Beard, Alice Gambel, 1954
  - Beardsley, Hezekiah, 1943
  - Beardwood, Joseph T., 1939, 1943
  - Bearn, A.G., 1959
  - Beatty, William K., 1957
  - Beausang, Michael, 1965
  - Beaven, Charles William, 1952
  - Beaven, Paul W., 1947-1956
  - Becht, Howell M., 1954
  - Beck, Mrs. William W., 1952
  - Becker, George H., 1952-1953
  - Becker, Jerrold M., 1952
  - Becker, Raymond J., 1946
  - Beckman, C. Herman, 1956
  - Beckman, Daryl E., 1962
  - Beeson, Paul B., 1940-1967
  - Beeson, R.A., 1959-1960
  - Behrend, Bernard, 1945, 1969
  - Behrend, Moses, 1961
  - Behrens, C.F., 1954
  - Beiler, J.M., 1965
  - Bell, A. Doyne, 1952-1953
  - Bell, Colin W., 1949
  - Bell, Mr. and Mrs. James Ford, 1966
  - Bell, William B., 1940-1947
  - Bellavance, Cyril D., 1946
  - Bellevue-Stratford, 1942
  - Bellhouse, Elen W., 1946
  - Belmonte, Carmelita, 1960
  - Bender, Joseph, 1954-1957
  - Benford, Robert J., 1969
  - Benglian, Sara D., 1970
  - Benison, Saul, 1964
  - Benjamin, Peter, 1959
  - Bennett, H. Stanley, 1961, 1963
  - Benny, Mrs. Joseph, 1951
  - Benson, Mrs. Charles, 1943
  - Benson, Purnell H., 1956, 1961
  - Berg, Robert L., 1962
  - Bergman, Charles C., 1969
  - Bergs, Victor, 1958
  - Bergsma, Daniel, 1951
  - Berk, J. Edward, 1949-1954
  - Berkel, Izzet, 1962
  - Berkley, Hugh E., 1939
  - Berkow, Elizabeth D., 1941
    Mrs. Samuel G.
  - Berman, Edgar F.
  - Berman, H.H., 1960
  - Berman, Peter H., 1959
  - Berners, Lewis, 1966
  - Bernese Alps Milk Company, 1948-1949
  - Bernhardt, David B., 1953
  - Bernheim, Bertram, 1945
  - Beronda, Mrs. Benny, 1957
  - Bernstein, Yale B., 1960-1971; 6.0 folders
  - Berry, George P., 1953, 1961-1966
  - Berson, Paul, 1949-1950
  - Bertelet, Helen F., 1940
  - Berthet, Etienne, 1971
  - Best, C.H., 1940
  - Beswick, Isobel, 1958-1959
  - Bethune, Donald S., 1955
  - Bevan, David C., 1968-1969
  - Beveridge, John, 1957
  - Beyer, Karl H., 1968
  - Bezreh, Anthony A., 1958
  - Bhanchet, Parttraporn, 1960
  - Bhavuche, Dr., 1961
  - Bicentennial Exposition, 1969-1971
  - Bickel, Horst, 1959
  - Bickford, E.D., 1941
  - Biddle, Margaret, 1953-1954
  - Biedermann, Dr., 1961
  - Biemesdorfer, Mary Ann, 1952-1953
  - Bierly, Mahlon Z., Jr., 1958
  - Bierman, Jessie M., 1939
  - Bierring, Walter L., 1960
  - Bigelow, Mrs. R.M., 1948
  - Biggs, John, Jr., 1968
  - Bigwood, E.J., 1943-1946
  - Bigwood, Francine, 1949
  - Bill, Audrey A., 1950-1959
  - Billingham, Rupert E., 1963
  - Bills before Congress, 1945-1946, 1951-1963; 2.0 folders
  - Binder, Theodor, 1959
  - Binns, Arthur W., 1957-1958
  - Biocca, Saul M., 1969
  - Bird, Roberto, 1942
  - Bishop, Eugene L., 1955-1957
  - Bishop, Harry C., 1955-1965
  - Bishop, Lloyd W., 1950
  - Bivings, Lee, Undated
  - Bixby, Lovell, 1949-1951
  - Bjorneboe, M., 1950-1968
  - Black, William C., 1948, 1955
  - Blackfan, Kenneth D., 1932-1933, 1940-1942
  - Blackiston Company, 1945
  - Blackman, Mrs. Conrad, 1967
  - Blackman, Edward, 1946
  - Blaine, Graham B., Jr., 1960
  - Blair, Franklin, 1966
  - Blair, Harry Edwin, 1942-1964
  - Blair, William Campbell, 1951-1952
  - Blaisdell, Richard K., 1966
  - Blake, Donald, 1953
  - Blake, Francis G., 1946
  - Blake, James M., 1943-1944
  - Blakemore, William S., 1964, 1969
  - Blanc, William A., 1958
  - Blanchard, Mercer, 1946-1951
  - Blank, Harvey, 1950-1951
  - Blankenship, M.W., 1953
  - Blattner, Russell J., 1951-1958
  - Blauvelt, G. Laurence, 1968
  - Blazey, Arthur G., 1958-1959
  - Bliss, Eleanor, 1957
  - Blitz, Daniel, 1950
  - Bliven, Bruce, 1952
  - Blodgett, F.M., 1959-1960
  - Blondheim, Dr., 1951
  - Blount, Frederick A., 1946-1959
  - Bluemle, Lewis, 1966, 1969
  - Blum, Werner M., 1965
  - Blumgart, Herrman L., 1948
  - Blumstein, George I., 1959, 1968
  - Blundell, George P., 1961
  - Boardman, Donnell W., 1957
  - Boardman, Elizabeth H., 1960
  - Bock, Arlie, 1946-1947
  - Bocking, D., 1968-1969; 2.0 folders
    University of Western Ontario.
  - Bockris, John, 1958
  - Bockus, Henry L., 1952-1970
  - Bode, William T., 1959
  - Bodian, David, 1950-1962
  - Bodian, Martin, 1948
  - Bodine, Cornelius, 1967
  - Bodine, John W., 1959-1961
  - Bodis-Wollner, Ivan, 1966-1967
  - Boger, William P., 1952
  - Boggs, Joseph D., 1954-1961
  - Boggs, Robert, 1964
  - Boggs, Thomas R., Jr., 1951-1971; 2.0 folders
  - Boines, George, J., 1947
  - Boinnard, Helene M., 1945, 1947
  - Boitnott, John K., 1966
  - Bok, Curtis and Nellie Lee, 1956, 1966-1967
  - Boles, Russell, 1947
  - Bolton, David M., 1969
  - Bomberger, John H.A., 1959
  - Bondy, Philip, Undated
  - Bongiovanni, Alfred M., 1947-1972, undated; 7.0 folders
  - Bonnel, P.H., 1956
  - Bonnem, Mrs. Alan M., 1966
  - Bonner, Bernice, 1939
  - Bonnin, Otto, 1962
  - Bonsel, W. Roscoe, 1941
  - Boorse, J.W., 1967
  - Boothby, Willard S., 1941
  - Borden Award, 1961
  - Borden Company, 1949-1956
  - Bordentown, New Jersey, 1949, 1952
  - Borowsky, Sydney, 1949
  - Borst, George H., 1941
  - Borton, Hugh, 1956-1969
  - Borton, Samuel L., 1965
  - Bortz, Edward L., 1946, 1949
  - Borum, Anne, 1956-1957
  - Borzell, Francis F., 1940-1949
  - Bosien, Marian Kreider, 1948
  - Bosma, James F., 1955-1959
  - Bottolfson, Judith, 1948
  - Boucot, Katharine R., 1961, 1966
  - Boulding, Kenneth, 1971
  - Boverman, Maxwell, 1940-1941
  - Bowen, Edwyn T., 1958-1961
  - Bower, Russell, 1956
  - Bowerman, Walter, 1952
  - Bowers, F. Clyde, 1957
  - Bowers, J.R., 1954, 1956
  - Bowler, John P., 1945
  - Bowman, John S., 1947
  - Boyd, Charles W., 1956
  - Boyd, Clara, 1943
  - Boyd, Howard, 1951
  - Boyden, Judith, 1952-1953
  - Boyer, Francis, 1959-1967
  - Bracken, E.C., 1960
  - Bradbury, Althea, 1927, 1969
    With regard to her husband, Dr. Samuel Bradbury.
  - Bradbury, Emilie, 1949-1950
  - Bradford, William L., 1949-1959
  - Bradley, Alison, 1952
  - Bradley, Basil V., 1964
  - Bradley, Charles, 1949
  - Bradley, J. Edmund, 1950-1956
  - Bradley, Stanley, 1964, 1967
  - Bradley, William, 1964
  - Bradley, William H., 1945-1952
  - Bradley, William N., 1947, 1960
  - Brady, John Paul, 1969
  - Brainerd, John G., 1964
  - Brandmiller, Barclay M., 1946
  - Branson, Julia E., 1966
  - Brashear, D.S., 1955
  - Brasted, Eric P., 1954
  - Braun, Fred C., 1959-1961
  - Braunwald, Eugene, 1965
  - Breitweiser, Ruth, 1943
  - Brennemann, Joseph, 1944-1954
  - Brenner, Rae, 1943
  - Brent, Robert L., 1965-1966
  - Bresette, G.E., 1953-1954
  - Breslaw, Leonard, 1966
  - Bresnan, Michael J., 1962
  - Bressler, Marvin, 1959-1963, undated
  - Brettner, Mary Hazel, 1939
  - Brice, C. Frederick, 1940
  - Bridge, Edward M., 1946
  - Bridgers, John D., 1954-1970; 2.0 folders
  - Brignola, Carolyn Veronica, 1952
  - Brinton, Samuel T., 1941
  - Briody, B.A., 1948, 1952
  - Briskier, Arthur A., 1941-1956
  - Brissaud, Henri Edouard, Undated
  - Britt, Louis P., 1959
  - Brittain, James, 1959
  - Britten, Sidney A., 1966-1967
  - Broadhurst, Miriam G., 1949
  - Brobeck, John R., 1952
  - Brock, Mary H., 1946-1948
  - Brodribb, H.S., 1952
  - Brodsky, Emanuel D., 1950-1954
  - Brodsky, William Aaron, 1944-1950
  - Brody, Virginia, 1941
  - Brokow, Doris M., 1941
  - Brokman, Henry, 1958-1959
  - Bromer, Alice R., Undated
  - Bromer, Ralph S., 1952-1953
  - Bromley-Davenport, Lenette Jeanes, 1944-1945
  - Bronk, Detlev W., 1942-1970
  - Brook, Karl Rex, 1963
  - Brooke and Company, 1959
  - Brooks, Carter, 1964
  - Brooks, Glidden, 1953-1954
  - Brooks, Mary McLeod, 1955
  - Brooks, Susie, 1946
  - Brooks, Walter, 1949
  - Brorby, Robert P., 1966
  - Brosin, Henry W., 1968
  - Brother, George M., 1949-1951
  - Brown, Alan, 1941-1949
  - Brown, Cabot, 1959
  - Brown, Charles H., 1953, 1961
  - Brown, Elizabeth B., 1954
  - Brown, F. Sterling, 1962
  - Brown, George L., 1958
  - Brown, Mrs. Henry P., 1956
  - Brown, J. Carlisle, Undated
  - Brown, Madison B., 1954
  - Brown, Marie, 1956-1958
  - Brown, Milton H., 1955
  - Brown, Mrs. Philip, 1947
  - Brown, Robert, 1945
  - Brown, W.E., 1943
  - Browne, J.S.L., 1952
  - Browne, Marie Julia, 1955
  - Browning, Betsy, 1971
  - Browning, Corbit, 1946
  - Browning, W.H., 1940
  - Brownlee, William M., 1942
  - Brownstein, Morris D., 1968
  - Brozek, Josef, 1962
  - Brubaker, Earl W., 1945
  - Bruce, Gene K., 1961
  - Bruce, James W., 1961
  - Bruce, Laetitia, 1954
  - Bruck, Erika, 1945
  - Brunell, Philip A., 1967-1969
  - Brunschwig, Alexander, 1964
  - Bryce, Lucy, 1945
  - Bryson, Vernon, 1950
  - Buch, Noel T.F., 1945
  - Buck, Pearl S., 1949-1952
  - Buck, Mrs. Walter E., 1961
  - Buckley, John C., 1954
  - Buckman, Howard M., 1958
  - Buckman, Lewis T., 1951
  - Buerki, Robin C., 1946-1962
  - Buffum, Frederick C., 1941
  - Buffum, William P., 1946, 1961
  - Buist, Neil R.M., 1966-1967
  - Bukowski, Martin J., 1960, 1966
  - Buley, H.M., 1948
  - Bundesen, Herman N., 1949
  - Bundy, Walter E., 1952
  - Burchenal, Joseph, 1956
  - Burdick, William F., 1950
  - Burgess, Alex M., 1948
  - Burgess Publishing Company, 1964
  - Burgoon, Carroll F., 1954-1959
  - Burgoon, Jane S., 1952, 1955
  - Burket, Louis Clair, 1947-1948
  - Burley, E.W., 1966
  - Burlington County Trust Company, 1948, 1955
  - Burman, David, 1959
  - Burmeister, Mary R., 1962
  - Burnet, F. MacFarlane, 1949-1969
  - Burnett, George, 1940
  - Burnham, E. Lewis, 1942
  - Burns, Ira, 1946
  - Burns, Louis J., 1940
  - Burr, Pamela, 1945
  - Burroughs Wellcome and Company, 1953, 1955
  - Burstein, Frank, 1967
  - Burwell, C. Sidney, 1940, 1953-1954
  - Buser, F., 1959-1962
  - Business Week, 1955
  - Busser, Ralph C. Jr., 1955
  - Butchart, James Baird, 1946-1954
  - Butler, Allan M., 1942-1970; 2.0 folders
  - Butler, Charles H., 1948
  - Butler, Leroy J., 1948
  - Butson, Harry E., 1950-1959
  - Butt, Hugh R., 1961-1962
  - Butterfield, Victor L., 1966
  - Butterworth, John, 1964
  - Buttimore, Dennis J., 1964-1969
  - Butts, William S., 1957
  - Buynak, Eugene, 1966
  - Byers, Randolph K., 1950
  - Byrd, Dorothy, 1957
  - Bytheway, Thomas, 1950
  - Cadbury, Henry J., 1954-1959
  - Cadbury, Jane and William W., 1944-1946
  - Cadbury, William E., Jr., 1948-1949
  - Caddell, Joan, 1957-1971
  - Caddy, James A., 1949-1951
  - Caffey, John, 1950
  - Cahoon, Russell F., 1959
  - Cajano, Antonio, 1957
  - Caldwell, Ann, 1958
  - Caldwell, Dennis, 1952
  - Calendar and Chronicle, 1967
  - Callahan, Eileen, 1943
  - Callan, Thomas, Jr., 1962, 1969
  - Camarda, Joseph J., 1954
  - Cameron, Anna R., 1956
  - Cameron, Charles S., 1958
  - Cameron, J.F., 1951
  - Cameron, Molly, 1955
  - Cameron Surgical Specialty Company, 1945-1946
  - Camp Choconut, Undated
  - Camp Detrick, 1954
  - Camp, William P., 1965, 1970
  - Campbell, Alec G.M., 1962
  - Campbell, Archibald, 1944
  - Campbell, Edward H., 1951-1952
  - Campbell, George A., 1944
  - Campbell, Helen, 1961
  - Campbell, J. Moore, 1941, 1944
  - Campbell, Robert, 1956
  - Campbell Soup Company, 1936, 1945-1953
  - Canape, Frank, 1960